Your eyes, tell me how you want me
你在眼睛闪耀着告诉我你多想要我
I can feel it in your heart beat
我能从你的心跳感受到
I know you like what you see
你知道你喜欢你所看到的
Hold me, I'll give you all that you need
抱紧我  我会给你你想要的
Wrap your love around me
用你的爱把我包围起来
You're so excited,
你很激动
I can feel you getting hotter, oh baby
我能感受到你越来越热烈  哦  宝贝
I'll take you down, I'll take you down
我会拿下你  得到你
Where no one's ever gone before
这之前是没人能做到的事情
And if you want more, if you want more
如果你想要的更多  想要的更多
More, more
更多  更多
Then, Jump!
那就跳吧
For my love
为我的爱
Jump in!
投入地跳
And feel my touch
感受我的触碰
Jump, if you want to taste my kisses in the night then,
跳吧  如果你想在今晚尝尝我的吻的味道
Jump for my love
为我的爱而跳
I know my heart can make you happy
我知道我的心能让你愉悦
Jump in!
投入吧
You know these arms can feel you up
你知道我双臂能感受到你的
Jump, if you want to taste my kisses in the night then,
跳吧  如果你想在今晚尝尝这香唇的味道
Jump Jump! For my love
为我的爱而跳吧